<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<anime>
  <entry>
    <id>21</id>
    <title>One Piece</title>
    <english>One Piece</english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>0</episodes>
    <score>8.55</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Currently Airing</status>
    <start_date>1999-10-20</start_date>
    <end_date>0000-00-00</end_date>
    <synopsis>Gol D. Roger was known as the &amp;quot;Pirate King,&amp;quot; the strongest and most infamous being to have sailed the Grand Line. The capture and death of Roger by the World Government brought a change throughout the world. His last words before his death revealed the existence of the greatest treasure in the world, One Piece. It was this revelation that brought about the Grand Age of Pirates, men who dreamed of finding One Piece&amp;mdash;which promises an unlimited amount of riches and fame&amp;mdash;and quite possibly the pinnacle of glory and the title of the Pirate King.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Enter Monkey D. Luffy, a 17-year-old boy who defies your standard definition of a pirate. Rather than the popular persona of a wicked, hardened, toothless pirate ransacking villages for fun, Luffy&amp;rsquo;s reason for being a pirate is one of pure wonder: the thought of an exciting adventure that leads him to intriguing people and ultimately, the promised treasure. Following in the footsteps of his childhood hero, Luffy and his crew travel across the Grand Line, experiencing crazy adventures, unveiling dark mysteries and battling strong enemies, all in order to reach the most coveted of all fortunes&amp;mdash;One Piece.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/6/73245.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>459</id>
    <title>One Piece Movie 1</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece: The Movie</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.22</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2000-03-04</start_date>
    <end_date>2000-03-04</end_date>
    <synopsis>Woonan is the legendary Great Gold Pirate, earning the nickname after accumulating about 1/3 of the gold available in the world. Even after his disappearance, the tales of his gold being stashed away in a remote island continue to persist, a juicy target that other pirates lust for.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
One of the pirates going to great lengths to attain the treasure is El Drago. He and his crew have hunted down Woonan&amp;#039;s former crew members one by one, and along the way, they find the map that will take them to the hidden island.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The map is not all they come across; they also manage to come into contact with the straw hat pirates. After a short battle, Luffy and company are robbed and separated from one another. Now they must find a way to make it to the island before El Drago does and take the legendary treasure for themselves.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/5/20925.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>460</id>
    <title>One Piece Movie 2: Nejimaki-jima no Daibouken</title>
    <english>One Piece: Clockwork Island Adventure</english>
    <synonyms>One Piece: Nejimakijima no Bouken; One Piece: Nejimaki Shima no Bouken</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.29</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2001-03-03</start_date>
    <end_date>2001-03-03</end_date>
    <synopsis>Informed by the Thief Brothers his ship has been stolen by the Trump Kyoudai (Trump Siblings) who have set up base on Clockwork Island. Monkey D. Luffy, Captain of the Going Merry and aspiring Pirate King works with his crew - Ussop, Zoro, Sanji and Nami to battle their way up Clockwork Island to reclaim their ship.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/2/3299.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>461</id>
    <title>One Piece Movie 3: Chinjuu-jima no Chopper Oukoku</title>
    <english>One Piece: Chopper Kingdom of Strange Animal Island</english>
    <synonyms>One Piece: Chinjou Shima no Chopper Oukoku</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.14</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2002-03-02</start_date>
    <end_date>2002-03-02</end_date>
    <synopsis>The crew comes upon Crown Island where the animals can talk and they makes Chopper their new king. But there are human hunters there also looking for the legendary horns that will give the person who consumes it immense power. Luffy and friends must stop them from destroying this animal kingdom.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/8/6937.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>462</id>
    <title>One Piece Movie 4: Dead End no Bouken</title>
    <english>One Piece: Dead End</english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.71</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2003-03-01</start_date>
    <end_date>2003-03-01</end_date>
    <synopsis>Luffy and crew arrive at the harbour of Anabaru. The local casino is holding a competition in which the winner will obtain a huge monetary reward if he reaches the finishing line first. Nami is elated and decides to participate in the competition. However, there is a conspiracy going behind the competition and the mastermind is an ex-military commander, Gasparde. His plan is to lure all the pirates to the military base and send them to their deaths. Luffy and gang have to overcome the numerous tests and tribulations along the way to complete this dead-end adventure.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/10/20924.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>463</id>
    <title>One Piece Movie 5: Norowareta Seiken</title>
    <english>One Piece: The Curse of the Sacred Sword</english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.40</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2004-03-06</start_date>
    <end_date>2004-03-06</end_date>
    <synopsis>Luffy and crew go to an island searching for a legendary sword, said to be the most expensive in the world. Soon attacking marines and beautiful maidens split the crew. Zoro betrays the crew to help an old friend, Luffy and Usopp wander through a cave, and the rest help a village fight marines. When Zoro defeats Sanji he takes the sacred pearls that are the only defense against the evil sword that will plunge the world into darkness. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/2/25413.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>464</id>
    <title>One Piece Movie 6: Omatsuri Danshaku to Himitsu no Shima</title>
    <english>One Piece: Baron Omatsuri and the Secret Island</english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.75</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2005-03-05</start_date>
    <end_date>2005-03-05</end_date>
    <synopsis>The Straw Hat crew obtain an advertisement for a recreational island on the Grand Line run by the Baron Omatsuri. Luffy decides to take this opportunity to kick back and relax. Unfortunately, when they arrive at the island, they are asked to compete in contests through unity for access to relaxation. However, there seems to be a mysterious air on the island, as the Straw Hat Pirates begin to fight amongst themselves, while Robin, Chopper, and Luffy individually search for the secret behind Baron Omatsuri&amp;#039;s island.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/11/25415.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>465</id>
    <title>One Piece Movie 7: Karakuri-jou no Mecha Kyohei</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece The Movie: Karakurijou no Mecha Kyohei; One Piece: Karakuri Shiro no Mecha Kyohei; One Piece: The Giant Mechanical Soldier of Karakuri Castle; Karakuri Castle's Mecha Giant Soldier</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.42</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2006-03-04</start_date>
    <end_date>2006-03-04</end_date>
    <synopsis>The Straw Hat crew salvages a treasure chest from a sinking wreck, inside which they find an old lady. To get the pirates to take her home, she promises them the treasure of a golden crown on her island: Mecha Island. Upon arrival, the crew is attacked by the lord of the island but he has a change of heart and decides to seek their help to solve the mystery of the Golden Crown.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN, edited)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/9/20927.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>466</id>
    <title>One Piece: Taose! Kaizoku Ganzack</title>
    <english>One Piece: Defeat the Pirate Ganzack!</english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>6.84</score>
    <type>OVA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>1998-07-26</start_date>
    <end_date>1998-07-26</end_date>
    <synopsis>While Luffy and his crew of Zoro and Nami are starving on their small boat, they are attacked by a large monster. Nami is taken away, while Luffy and Zoro wash up on shore. There they meet a young girl, Medaka, and learn of the sad history of the island. The evil Pirate Ganzack has taken away all the men in the village and enslaved them, including Medaka's father. Now Luffy, Zoro, and Medaka must infiltrate Ganzack's base in order to rescue the villagers and Nami. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/12/37647.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>1094</id>
    <title>One Piece: Umi no Heso no Daibouken-hen</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Special: Adventure in the Ocean's Navel</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.40</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2000-12-20</start_date>
    <end_date>2000-12-20</end_date>
    <synopsis>The Straw Hats encounter a city in the middle of a whirlpool, called the Ocean's Navel, that is being destroyed by giant monsters. These monsters supposedly protect a treasure capable of granting wishes, but in the process of defeating these guardians, the crew ends up releasing another evil.  (aired after Episode 53)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: Wikipedia)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/6/20923.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>1237</id>
    <title>One Piece: Oounabara ni Hirake! Dekkai Dekkai Chichi no Yume!</title>
    <english>One Piece Special: Open Upon the Great Sea! A Father's Huge, HUGE Dream!</english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.39</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2003-04-06</start_date>
    <end_date>2003-04-06</end_date>
    <synopsis>The story opens on Pirate Zap's ship, where two of his crew, Bonnie and Max, are tired and want to escape, but unfortunately they have no money. Three children were being held captive on the ship overhear them. The eldest, Amanda, who's father was a pro treasure hunter, knows the whereabouts of a great treasure, and offers them a deal. If they help them make a clean escape, they could take all the treasure they wanted. They agree, and the five of them barely escape and make it onto a small island where they meet Luffy and his crew. Unfortunately they were pursued and Luffy and Amanda are captured and brought back to their boss, the head of the Bayan Pirates, who is also after the treasure. Now Luffy and the others must battle the Bayan pirates and find the treasure that Amanda's father had left for his children. Amanda, who has always resented adventure and treasure because her father was constantly gone in search for it, finally understands his feelings. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/6/20850.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>1238</id>
    <title>One Piece: Mamore! Saigo no Dai Butai</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece TV Special 3; One Piece Special: Protect! The Last Great Performance; Mamore! Saigo no Oobutai</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.46</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2003-12-14</start_date>
    <end_date>2003-12-14</end_date>
    <synopsis>For many years, Ex-Marine Lieutenant Randolph and his troupe have put on a play aboard his ship. Having lost his family to pirates, Randolph wishes to put on plays that will give courage to those who have also lost their loved ones to pirates. Unfortunately, Randolph must retire soon, and he is now giving his last performance. Luffy and his crew come to see the play, and somehow manage to take part in it themselves. But from Randolph's past comes a vengeful subordinate with a diabolical plan who has finally become commander in order to capture Randolph. Luffy and his nakama now must prove to the people that not all pirates are scum, and protect Randolph's final farewell performance from the bitter commander. (aired after Episode 174)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/5/77108.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>2020</id>
    <title>One Piece: Nenmatsu Tokubetsu Kikaku! Mugiwara no Luffy Oyabun Torimonochou</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Special: The Detective Memoirs of Chief Straw Hat Luffy</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.33</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2005-12-18</start_date>
    <end_date>2005-12-18</end_date>
    <synopsis>In an alternate reality world that resembles Edo Period Japan, Luffy acts as a member of the police. This is made up of two adventures: in the first, Buggy makes trouble in the town; in the second, a mysterious girl named Vivi appears (aired after Episode 253). This special contains several cameos from characters throughout the entire series. A second pair of episodes were aired after episode 290, continuing this story, as part of the New Year&amp;#039;s special.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/9/21651.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>2107</id>
    <title>One Piece Movie 8: Episode of Alabasta - Sabaku no Oujo to Kaizoku-tachi</title>
    <english>One Piece The Movie: Episode of Alabasta - The Desert Princess and the Pirates</english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.42</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2007-03-03</start_date>
    <end_date>2007-03-03</end_date>
    <synopsis>A retelling of the Alabasta arc.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/13/21760.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>2385</id>
    <title>One Piece: Jango no Dance Carnival</title>
    <english>One Piece: Django's Dance Carnival</english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.31</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2001-03-03</start_date>
    <end_date>2001-03-03</end_date>
    <synopsis>Luffy and his crew are on Mirror Ball Island during a dance carnival. They are spotted by Marines just as Jango the hypnotist is running from them. Luffy and the others are caught up in the dance carnival as Jango, in his desperate attempt to escape, hypnotizes the entire island to dance the night away.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/5/70887.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>2386</id>
    <title>One Piece: Yume no Soccer Ou!</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece: Dream Soccer King!; One Piece: Soccer King of Dreams</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.29</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2002-03-02</start_date>
    <end_date>2002-03-02</end_date>
    <synopsis>Luffy and his crew take on the Villain All-Stars in a game of soccer in order to become the Dream Soccer King. The game comes down to a pk tie-breaker shoot-out with Coby as goalie and Helmeppo refereeing.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN) </synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/4/70587.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>2490</id>
    <title>One Piece: Mezase! Kaizoku Yakyuu Ou</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece: Take Aim! The Pirate Baseball King</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.16</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2004-03-06</start_date>
    <end_date>2004-03-06</end_date>
    <synopsis>Luffy and crew takes on Arlong's crew in baseball. Announced by Bon Clay and Buggy.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/8/70593.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>2680</id>
    <title>One Piece: Straw Hat Theater</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Strawhat Theater; One Piece: Mugiwara Theater</synonyms>
    <episodes>5</episodes>
    <score>7.54</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2006-10-01</start_date>
    <end_date>2006-10-29</end_date>
    <synopsis>Straw Hat Theater is made up of five shorts that aired alongside One Piece episodes 279 through 283 in October 2006. They are based on Oda Eiichiro's side comics that were drawn when he was given three sheets of blank paper by his editor and told to draw anything.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The first short is about Chopper Man infiltrating the lair of the evil Dr. Usodabada. The second short is a news report on what food was like for the Straw Hats before Sanji joined the crew. The third short investigates the hypothetical situation of &amp;quot;if the Straw Hat Pirates were Obahan, who would be the strongest?&amp;quot; The fourth short is about the bosses of the Luffione, Zorocia, and Sanjino families fighting for control. In the fifth short, all of the Straw Hats are carefree monsters.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/8/70745.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>3848</id>
    <title>One Piece Movie 9: Episode of Chopper Plus - Fuyu ni Saku, Kiseki no Sakura</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece: Episode of Chopper Plus - Bloom in the Winter, Miracle Sakura</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.62</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2008-03-01</start_date>
    <end_date>2008-03-01</end_date>
    <synopsis>The movie is a retelling of the Drum Island arc with new music and animation. Vivi has been removed from the plot while both Nico Robin and Franky, who joined the crew after the Drum Island arc, have been added. The movie also has the Straw Hat&amp;#039;s new ship, the Thousand Sunny. It has been stated that Oda will be creating a new character for this movie, Wapol&amp;#039;s older brother, Mushul, who also appears to be a Devil Fruit user. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: Wikipedia) </synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/12/25414.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>4155</id>
    <title>One Piece Film: Strong World</title>
    <english>One Piece Film Strong World</english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Movie 10</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>8.35</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2009-12-12</start_date>
    <end_date>2009-12-12</end_date>
    <synopsis>Upon hearing news that islands in East Blue are being destroyed, Monkey D. Luffy and his crew go to investigate. On their way, however, an outlandish pirate ship appears out of the sky, helmed by the infamous pirate Shiki &amp;quot;the Golden Lion&amp;quot;&amp;mdash;a man who ate the Float-Float Fruit and the first ever prisoner to escape from Impel Down. In his quest to defeat the World Government, Shiki kidnaps Nami to be his own navigator and sends the rest of the Straw Hat Pirates to his floating islands as hostages, leaving her in a dilemma. Separated in a land under Shiki&amp;#039;s absolute control, Luffy and his crew must survive the mystifying terrain in order to bring back their navigator and friend.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/12/75894.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>5252</id>
    <title>One Piece: Romance Dawn Story</title>
    <english>One Piece: Romance Dawn Story</english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Prototype</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.51</score>
    <type>OVA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2008-11-24</start_date>
    <end_date>2008-11-24</end_date>
    <synopsis>The Straw Hat Pirates, searching for the great passage &amp;quot;Grand Line&amp;quot;, are in trouble when their food runs out! Luffy, searching for food on his own, finds a ship belonging to the pirate, Gary, and takes it over!! He lands at a nearby town...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Luffy was attacked by a young girl, Silk, who mistook him for a member of the other pirate gang. As the two eat a meal, they tell their stories. Meanwhile, Gary and his band are burning with anger at Luffy, demanding payment from the town's defenseless citizens...!!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: jumpland.com/animetour/op/index_en.html)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/6/11300.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>8171</id>
    <title>One Piece Recap</title>
    <english>One Piece Recap</english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Recap OVA</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.32</score>
    <type>OVA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2010-03-17</start_date>
    <end_date>2010-03-17</end_date>
    <synopsis>A recap OVA summarizing the ten-year TV series up to the Impel Down arc.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/9/20706.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>8740</id>
    <title>One Piece Film: Strong World Episode 0</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>8.13</score>
    <type>OVA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2010-04-00</start_date>
    <end_date>2010-04-00</end_date>
    <synopsis>Set over 20 years prior to the main One Piece story, this limited release OVA chronicles the confrontation between Gold Lion Shiki and Gold Roger as well as other events around the world around the time of the Pirate King's execution. </synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/2/24152.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>9999</id>
    <title>One Piece 3D: Mugiwara Chase</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece 3D: Strawhat Chase; One Piece Movie 11</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.27</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2011-03-19</start_date>
    <end_date>2011-03-19</end_date>
    <synopsis>According to Weekly Shonen Jump, 3D movies of One Piece and Toriko were announced to premiere on March 19th, 2011. One Piece 3D is an original story about the missing straw hat of Luffy. </synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/4/32455.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>10033</id>
    <title>Toriko</title>
    <english>Toriko</english>
    <synonyms>Toriko (2011); Toriko (TV); Toriko x One Piece Collabo Special</synonyms>
    <episodes>147</episodes>
    <score>7.71</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2011-04-03</start_date>
    <end_date>2014-03-30</end_date>
    <synopsis>Hamburgers that grow out of the ground like four-leaf clovers, mountain ranges carved out of ice cream, and warm servings of mac and cheese that stew deep within the stomachs of volcanoes fill the landscape. This world of delectable natural wonders has reached a prime age of exploration&amp;mdash;the Gourmet Age! Citizens and chefs alike aspire to taste and prepare the finest dishes, while adventurers called &amp;quot;Gourmet Hunters&amp;quot; seek out delicious rare ingredients.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Possessing a unique set of skills, the wild and passionate Gourmet Hunter Toriko is infamous for discovering 2% of all known ingredients. Together with his friend Komatsu&amp;mdash;a highly skilled chef working at a five-star hotel&amp;mdash;Toriko strives to complete his Full Course Menu of Life. But it isn&amp;rsquo;t going to be easy; in order to obtain the most delicious ingredients, Toriko must battle against obstacles like deadly monsters, evil organizations, and food itself!  &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/12/56329.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>12001</id>
    <title>One Piece 3D: Gekisou! Trap Coaster</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.28</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2011-12-01</start_date>
    <end_date>2011-12-01</end_date>
    <synopsis>Toei Animation released a new 3D anime short at events starting December 1, 2011. The short run about 12 minutes long and played at stereoscopic 3D theaters at Aichi Prefecture's Lagunasia theme park, Nagasaki Prefecture's Huis Ten Bosch theme park, Kanagawa Prefecture's Yokohama Landmark Tower, and Hiroshima Prefecture's NTT CRED Hall.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)&lt;br /&gt;
</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/4/33839.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>12859</id>
    <title>One Piece Film: Z</title>
    <english>One Piece Film Z</english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Movie 12</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>8.34</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2012-12-15</start_date>
    <end_date>2012-12-15</end_date>
    <synopsis>The Straw Hat Pirates enter the rough seas of the New World in search of the hidden treasures of the Pirate King, Gol D. Roger－One Piece. On their voyage, the pirates come across a terrifying, powerful man, former Marine Admiral Z.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Z is accused of having stolen the &amp;quot;Dyna Stones&amp;quot;, weapons believed to have the power to shake up the New World. The Marine Headquarters believes Z is about to use it to end the pirate era, and with it, the lives of many innocent people. In fear of such a phenomenal event, marines start to take action against the former admiral.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Even if it means stumbling upon marines and the navy, the Straw Hat Pirates decided to chase after Z and stop him from causing havoc. As they continue to embark on their ventures, the pirates bump into new and familiar acquaintances.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/6/44297.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>15323</id>
    <title>One Piece: Episode of Nami - Koukaishi no Namida to Nakama no Kizuna</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Special; Episode of Nami: Tears of a Navigator and the Bonds of Friends</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>8.24</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2012-08-25</start_date>
    <end_date>2012-08-25</end_date>
    <synopsis>A retelling of the Arlong Park arc, with new animation.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/5/41415.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>16143</id>
    <title>One Piece: Kinkyuu Kikaku One Piece Kanzen Kouryakuhou</title>
    <english>One Piece: Emergency Planning, A Perfect Strategy for the One Piece</english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Recap</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.32</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>1999-12-22</start_date>
    <end_date>1999-12-22</end_date>
    <synopsis>This is the first recapitulation episode, covering the first five episodes with only the difference being that the episode follows the manga storyline and begins with Luffy and Shanks at the bar. Also, in the ending, the current Straw Hats have a small conversation about their goals.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: One Piece Wikia)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/6/44259.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>16239</id>
    <title>One Piece: Episode of Luffy - Hand Island no Bouken</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece: Episode of Luffy - Hand Island Adventure</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.82</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2012-12-15</start_date>
    <end_date>2012-12-15</end_date>
    <synopsis>The story of the Hand Island no Bouken special is set a little before the events of One Piece Film Z and depicts a major &amp;quot;Hand Island&amp;quot; incident during the New World storyline. The story is set at &amp;quot;Cannon Town&amp;quot; where a parent and a child work as craftspeople. The incident revolves around them and a commodore of a marine base. The special will also have a flashback scene to the story in the first chapter of the manga, but with new animation. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN) </synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/8/52463.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>16287</id>
    <title>One Piece: Romance Dawn</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.58</score>
    <type>OVA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2012-12-20</start_date>
    <end_date>2012-12-20</end_date>
    <synopsis>Bundled with the PSP pirate romance role-playing game One Piece Romance Dawn: Bouken no Yoake (ワンピース ロマンスドーン 冒険の夜明け).&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Note: This game is not based on &amp;quot;Romance Dawn,&amp;quot; Oda Eiichirou&amp;#039;s prototype manga for what would eventually become One Piece. Instead, the title reflects the fact that the game covers the &amp;quot;Romance Dawn&amp;quot; arc of the manga, at the &amp;quot;dawn&amp;quot; of pirate Luffy&amp;#039;s adventures in the East Blue.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/4/71053.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>16468</id>
    <title>One Piece: Glorious Island</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Special: Glorious Island</synonyms>
    <episodes>2</episodes>
    <score>7.32</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2012-12-23</start_date>
    <end_date>2012-12-30</end_date>
    <synopsis>An exclusive anime prologue to One Piece Film Z with an original story penned by manga creator Eiichiro Oda. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN) </synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/7/85476.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>19123</id>
    <title>One Piece: Episode of Merry - Mou Hitori no Nakama no Monogatari</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Special; One Piece: Episode of Merry - The Tale of One More Friend</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>8.28</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2013-08-24</start_date>
    <end_date>2013-08-24</end_date>
    <synopsis>The story arcs aboard the Straw Hat Crew&amp;#039;s first ship Going Merry (Merry Go in some adaptations) are recreated with brand-new animation, from Luffy and Usopp&amp;#039;s fight and Robin&amp;#039;s disappearance to the crew&amp;#039;s final farewell to the ship. Going Merry is treated as another member of the Straw Hats as Luffy, Zoro, Nami, and the rest of the crew set sail for the legendary treasure, the One Piece.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/9/61015.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>20871</id>
    <title>Nissan Serena x One Piece 3D: Mugiwara Chase - Sennyuu!! Sauzando Sanii-gou</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Serena x One Piece; One Piece 3D Mugiwara Chase: Infiltration! Thousand Sunny!; Brook Introduces The Thousand Sunny</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.01</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2011-03-05</start_date>
    <end_date>2011-03-05</end_date>
    <synopsis>Brook introduces the Thousand Sunny&amp;#039;s while Luffy searches for his straw hat.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This was a special included in a limited edition DVD that was released in Nissan stores across Japan. The DVD also included the making of One Piece 3D: Straw Hat Chase.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/2/55695.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>22661</id>
    <title>One Piece: Cry Heart</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece: Banpresto's &quot;Cry Heart&quot; Short; Fuyujima ni Furu Sakura; Children's Dream; Ace no Saigo</synonyms>
    <episodes>3</episodes>
    <score>6.79</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2014-01-19</start_date>
    <end_date>2015-04-22</end_date>
    <synopsis>Episode 1: Fuyujima ni Furu Sakura&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Diligent animators took Banpresto's &amp;quot;One Piece Cry heart ~Fuyujima ni Furu Sakura~&amp;quot; (One Piece Cry heart ~The Cherry Blossoms That Fall on Winter Island~) line of crane game prize figures and created a five-minute stop-motion short. The short recreates the famous &amp;quot;Hiluluk's Cherry Blossoms&amp;quot; scene from Eiichiro Oda's manga and anime One Piece.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Episode 2: Fuyujima ni Furu Sakura&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A stop-motion animated video for Banpresto's &amp;quot;One Piece Cry heart ~children's dream~&amp;quot; line of crane game prize figures. The short recreates the famous &amp;quot;Oath of Brothers&amp;quot; scene from Eiichiro Oda's manga and anime.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Episode 3: Ace no Saigo&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/13/60173.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>25161</id>
    <title>One Piece 3D2Y: Ace no shi wo Koete! Luffy Nakama Tono Chikai</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Special 15th Anniversary</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>8.06</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2014-08-30</start_date>
    <end_date>2014-08-30</end_date>
    <synopsis>The special takes place during the two year before the Straw Hats reunite on Sabaody. Luffy is currently in Rusukaina training to get stronger to take on the New World. However the training is interrupted when Hancock&amp;#039;s sisters, Marigold and Sandersonia, are kidnapped by the Byrnndi World, a pirate who was locked away on Level 6 of Impel Down but escaped during Luffy&amp;#039;s invasion to save Ace, in order to lure Hancock to him and use her as a hostage against the World Government due to her Shichibukai status. Thus Luffy and Hancock head off to confront him and save Hancock&amp;#039;s sisters.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: One Piece Wiki)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/3/64755.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>28683</id>
    <title>One Piece: Episode of Alabasta - Prologue</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.40</score>
    <type>OVA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2007-03-03</start_date>
    <end_date>2007-03-03</end_date>
    <synopsis>Prologue to the movie, showing the Whiskey Peak arc. Released as an OVA.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: AniDB)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/12/69239.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>31289</id>
    <title>One Piece: Episode of Sabo - 3 Kyoudai no Kizuna Kiseki no Saikai to Uketsugareru Ishi</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.79</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2015-08-22</start_date>
    <end_date>2015-08-22</end_date>
    <synopsis>The special will revisit the childhood past of the three sworn brothers Luffy, Ace, and Sabo, when they all dreamed of becoming pirates. In addition, it will depict how Sabo originally came into the kingdom of Dressrosa (which was not depicted in Eiichiro Oda&amp;#039;s original manga or the television anime), as well as his reunion with Luffy from his point of view.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/2/75887.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>31490</id>
    <title>One Piece Film: Gold</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Movie 13</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>8.17</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2016-07-23</start_date>
    <end_date>2016-07-23</end_date>
    <synopsis>In One Piece Film Gold, The Straw Hats are at it again in an all-new high-flying adventure! A gripping tale unfolds in the spectacular city of Gran Tesoro, where Luffy and his crew are drawn by dreams of hitting the jackpot. With so much luck, Luffy&amp;#039;s winning streak can&amp;#039;t possibly end. But behind the gilded curtains lies a powerful king whose deep pockets and deeper ambitions spell disaster for all.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: FUNimation)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/12/81081.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>32051</id>
    <title>One Piece: Adventure of Nebulandia</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Special</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.45</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2015-12-19</start_date>
    <end_date>2015-12-19</end_date>
    <synopsis>This special will have the Straw Hats fight Foxy again in the New World on Nebulandia, an island that nullifies Devil Fruit powers.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/5/77050.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>32437</id>
    <title>One Piece: Long Ring Long Land-hen</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>One Piece: Long Ring Long Land Arc - A One Night Abridged Special; Episode of Foxy; One Piece: Long Ring Long Land-hen - Ichiya Kagiri no Tokubetsu Henshuu-ban</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>6.96</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2015-12-11</start_date>
    <end_date>2015-12-11</end_date>
    <synopsis>A 75-minute recap of episodes 207-219, the Long Ring Long Land Arc. </synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/12/83503.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>33338</id>
    <title>One Piece: Heart of Gold</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.67</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2016-07-16</start_date>
    <end_date>2016-07-16</end_date>
    <synopsis>Prequel to [i]One Piece Film: Gold[/i].</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/6/80109.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>33606</id>
    <title>One Piece Film: Gold Episode 0 - 711 ver.</title>
    <english>ONE PIECE FILM GOLD 〜episode 0〜 711ver.</english>
    <synonyms>One Piece Film: Gold Episode 0</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.17</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2016-07-02</start_date>
    <end_date>2016-07-02</end_date>
    <synopsis>A short prequel to [i]One Piece Film: Gold[/i] featuring the nine Straw hat crew members on the ship, planning what to do when they arrive the Casino.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/4/83792.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>34165</id>
    <title>Oishi-sa Hajikeru! One Piece</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Fanta</synonyms>
    <episodes>0</episodes>
    <score>6.24</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Currently Airing</status>
    <start_date>2016-09-11</start_date>
    <end_date>0000-00-00</end_date>
    <synopsis>A collaboration between Fanta and [i]One Piece[/i]. The first episode features Luffy and Chopper rapping with Fanta Grape and Fanta Orange respectively in hand.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/12/82171.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>36215</id>
    <title>One Piece: Episode of East Blue - Luffy to 4-nin no Nakama no Daibouken</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>8.02</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2017-08-26</start_date>
    <end_date>2017-08-26</end_date>
    <synopsis>The words that Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, uttered just before his death excited the masses and the world has entered a Great Pirate Era! There is a group of young pirates who are about to set sail on the Grand Line. Monkey D. Luffy, a rubber man. Roronoa Zoro aka &amp;ldquo;Pirate Hunter.&amp;rdquo; Usopp, a sniper. Sanji, a seafaring cook. And &amp;ldquo;Cat Burglar&amp;rdquo; Nami. They, the Straw Hats, all place a foot upon a barrel and make their vows before their next journey across the great ocean. Luffy shouts &amp;ldquo;In order to be the King of the Pirates!&amp;rdquo; A decade ago in the Windmill Village... A little boy Luffy was enthralled with a pirate boss Red-Haired Shanks. But a group of mountain bandits shows up and makes fun of the pirates. &amp;ldquo;Why didn&amp;#039;t you fight them?!&amp;rdquo; Luffy yells out angrily but Shanks says that it&amp;#039;s nothing worth getting mad over. At that time, Luffy snatches the Gum-Gum Fruit from a treasure box and eats it and as a result, his entire body becomes rubber and he loses the ability to swim for the rest of his life! A few days later, Luffy is surrounded by the mountain bandits again and Shanks comes to help. &amp;ldquo;No matter what the reason, anyone who hurts my friends has to pay!!&amp;rdquo; Shanks and his pirate crew are incredibly strong and they beat down the mountain bandits. Higuma, the head of the mountain bandits, runs away kidnapping Luffy and heads for the sea. However, they encounter a local Sea Monster there and are attacked. Luffy is in a desperate situation... But again, Shanks saves the day. He outstares the Sea Monster and chases it away but in exchange, he loses his left arm... When Shanks leaves the village, he leaves his straw hat with Luffy. &amp;ldquo;Come bring it back to me someday! Once you&amp;#039;ve become a great pirate!&amp;rdquo; 10 years later, Luffy has grown up strong and he sets out for an adventure on a small boat. He again encounters the local Sea Monster for that fateful day. However, Luffy takes it down with a single blow of Gum-Gum Pistol. Luffy&amp;rsquo;s journey to become the King of the Pirates now begins!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: Crunchyroll)</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/10/87473.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>36239</id>
    <title>Sono Me ga Mitsumeru Mono</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Sante FX x One Piece; That Which Our Eyes Gaze Upon</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>5.41</score>
    <type>ONA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2017-06-19</start_date>
    <end_date>2017-06-19</end_date>
    <synopsis>A web-exclusive collaboration between [i]Santen[/i] an eye drops company and [i]One Piece[/i]. The commercial is promoting the new [i]Sante FX[/i] eye drops in a stylish Luffy model and Trafalgar Law model. On October 31, 2017 another commercial was released with the same animation but showcasing a Sanji model and Zoro model instead.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/2/87540.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>36240</id>
    <title>Scratch x One Piece Film: Gold</title>
    <english>Scratch x One Piece Film: Gold</english>
    <synonyms>Takarakuji</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>5.75</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2016-00-00</start_date>
    <end_date>2016-00-00</end_date>
    <synopsis>A TV collaboration between [i]One Piece Film: Gold[/i] and Takarakuji the nationwide lottery system in Japan. The commercial is promoting lottery scratch cards with One Piece designs on them.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/8/87541.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>36241</id>
    <title>One Piece Film: Gold - Cine Mike Popcorn Kokuchi</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>TOHO Cinemas x One Piece Film: Gold</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>5.92</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2016-00-00</start_date>
    <end_date>2016-00-00</end_date>
    <synopsis>A TV collaboration between [i]One Piece Film: Gold[/i] and TOHO Cinemas for the latter&amp;#039;s grilled corn flavored popcorn being made for the former&amp;#039;s nationwide film release. </synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/2/87542.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>36242</id>
    <title>TOHO Cinemas x One Piece Film: Gold - Tokubetsu Eizou</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>6.00</score>
    <type>ONA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2016-02-29</start_date>
    <end_date>2016-02-29</end_date>
    <synopsis>A collaboration between [i]One Piece Film: Gold[/i] and TOHO Cinemas. It features the One Piece cast in a manga sakuga style batting around ball which then becomes gold colored with the cast gaining their colored anime film&amp;#039;s design too. The golden ball then turns into the TOHO Cinemas logo as Luffy holds it out to the viewer.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Eiichiro Oda himself supervised the collaboration to give the most manga-art accurate imagery possible.</synopsis>
    <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/3/87543.jpg</image>
  </entry>
</anime>
